

PROFILE

Self-directed & motivated Professional with almost 6+ years of work experience in UI Development using Technologies of HTML, CSS & JavaScript.

Professional working experience of web development including requirements of gathering information, designing, implementation, deployment & support.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+91-8586914425

EMAIL:

singh.jyoti.bist@gmail.com

ADDRESS:

Bangalore, India

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jyotising hfrontenddeveloper/

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Programming Languages/Scripts: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Java(core)

Frameworks/Libraries:

BootStrap, JQuery, React.is

Application/Platforms/Web Server:

Xampp, Cloud, Node.is, GIT

Databases/Queues:

SQL,MySQL,MongoDB

CMS: WordPress

IDE/Editors: VSC, Sublime **Tools:** Figma, Photoshop, CorelDraw, Canva

JYOTI SINGH

Frontend Developer | UI UX

WORK EXPERIENCE

Deputy Manager (Band-II)

ICICI Bank Ltd, Dec. 2021 - Present

- Develop identified user stories, with considerations of security
- Build solutions, resolve glitches & implement scalable solutions in technology for secure &smooth users journey
- Collaborate & discuss issues with other teams for resolution
- Develop code and adhere to performance, security and compliance metrics for the applications

WEB- Developer | Designer & DM executive

Addontrip Pvt Ltd, Jan. 2020 - Dec. 2021

- To design & develop the responsive websites for Google Ads
- Translate design wireframes into UI code with feature of Responsive Design & Accessibility
- To test the developed project & deploy solutions
- Support & Maintain the smooth functioning of application.
- To implement the required changes in website/application.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Aakash Educational Services Pvt. Ltd., Jan. 2014 - Mar. 2017

- To design, develop & maintain responsiveness of the websites, page speed & browser compatibility.
- Produce the student friendly application and do their Testing (UI/UX) for various devices.

EDUCATION

Post-Graduation (2017 -2019): MTTM with 8.3 CGPA Banaras Hindu University, Varanasi, India

Graduation (2009 -2013): Bachelor of Engg. (ECE) with 72.78 % Bansal Institute of Sc. & Tech., RGPV, Bhopal, India

Higher Sec. School (2007 -2008): Science (PCM) with 71.5 % Saint Mary's Higher Sec School Chakghat Rewa, MP, India

High School (2005 -2006): Science with 87.6 % Saint Mary's High School, Chakghat Rewa, MP, India

TECHNICAL SKILLS CERTIFICATION

Certification in Web-Designing & Development.

Certification in Meta Professional Front-end Developer.

Certification in MERN Full Stack Web Development.

Certification in C++ through C.

Certification in Google Foundation of Project Management.